Maxwell Conway

maxconway23@gmail.com | 561-654-6926 | Atlanta, GA (Open to relocation or remote)

LinkedIn: https://www.linkedin.com/in/maxwell-conway-200x/

Github: https://github.com/MaxwellConway. Portfolio Website: https://github.com/MaxwellConway. Portfolio Website: https://maxwellconway.github.io/.

SUMMARY

Detail-oriented and organized Software and IT Specialist with a background in full-stack development. Excels in systemic thinking and problem-solving, with a commitment to understanding how technologies function within larger structures. Currently pursuing CompTIA A+ Certification to complement programming skills.

SKILLS

Programming Languages: JavaScript, TypeScript, Python *Front-End Technologies*: HTML, CSS

Web Development: React, Node.js, Express Database Management: PostgreSQL, Sequelize

EDUCATION

CompTIA A+ Certification (in progress)

CompTIA 02/2024-Present

Software Development Bootcamp, Full-Time

DigitalCrafts | Atlanta, GA

08/2023

• 17-week full time bootcamp focused on front-end and back-end development

Bachelor of Science - BA, Political Science

Florida State University

12/2020

Projects

GamerNet 08/2023

- https://gamernet.netlifv.app/
- https://dev.to/maxwellconway/gamernet-lfm
- Acted as Project Manager Uses React, Supabase, Tailwind to create a social platform for gaming.

Elden Ring Wiki Tool

05/2023

- https://github.com/MaxwellConway/Front-End-Project
- https://dev.to/maxwellconway/elden-ring-weapons-incantations-sorceries-a-front-end-project-c0c
- Uses public API to display data and link to corresponding wiki url

EXPERIENCE

Cleveland Electric

Electrician

12/2021 - 2/2023

• Entrusted to complete projects with minimal supervision and used leadership skills and

- teamwork to install networking cables within given timeframes
 Communicated effectively with other team members from various backgrounds to problem-solve and complete projects within a given timeframe.
- Continued education with weekly electrical theory coursework

Florida Department of State, Division of Corporations

04/2019 - 01/2021